所以我在这儿有个小部分就是要注意的是吧
So I have a little section here
just to note on expose, right?
到目前为止我们讨论的是出版，对吧 ?
So far we've been talking
about using publish, right?
如果你看看这把它关掉
So if you look here, shut that down.
我用的是 3000:3000 ，是吗 ?
I've been using publish 3000:3000, right?
从技术上来说我可以说 EXPOSE
You can technically write in here,
I could say EXPOSE,
3000 我可以暴露 3000
3000 and I can expose 3000.
完全可以
It totally would work.
所以我们来解决这个问题
So let's get rid of this.
这里的问题是首先我还是要用旗子来做，
The issue here is first of all,
I still have to run it with a flag,
那是什么
which is, What is it?
好了，这就开始了，实际上，让我们这样做，所以它就很附着。
Okay, so that's running, and actually,
let's do it this way, so it just attaches.
所以，我要先建它，让我们造它吧。
So, I have to build it first,
let's build it.
我救了吗
Did I save that?
是否运行 EXPOSE?
Did it run EXPOSE?
而且是正确的
And the correct one.
不我错了这就是原因
No, I'm in the wrong one, that's why.
用于更复杂的节点应用程序的 Docker 文件。
Docker file for more complicated node app.
然后我会说 EXPOSE 3000 ，我要再建造一次。
And then here I'm gonna say EXPOSE 3000,
and I'm gonna build it again.
然后，我再次尝试运行我的节点应用程序。
And then I try and run my node app again.
但我要在没有公布的情况下运行
But I'm gonna run it without publish.
我要说的是分开的所以它是在后台运行的
I'm gonna say detached, so
it's running in the background.
现在如果我说停手
Now, if I say docker ps.
首先，如果我试着到这里，去 localhost:3000，
First of all if I try and
go over in here and go to localhost:3000,
那就不起作用了吧
it's not gonna work, right?
因为它在技术上并不暴露在那个端口上。
Cuz it's not actually technically
exposed on that particular port.
所以你要做的就是告诉 Docker ， Docker 杀，
So what you actually have to do is
you have to tell docker, docker kill,
我刚刚运行了我的节点应用程序
this one that I just ran my node app.
这就是你的形象对吧
That's the image, right?
所以你必须要杀了这条路
So you have to kill this way.
Docker 会终止的。
Docker kill that.
>> 神秘之旅。
&gt;&gt; Mystifying journey.
> > 那是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; What's that?
>> 这个名字神秘的旅程
&gt;&gt; The name of it, mystifying journey.
>> 对，对，也行。
&gt;&gt; Right, yeah, that will work too.
所以你必须这样做，让我看看我是否能在码头上运行 --帮助。
So you have to do it with,
let me see if I can docker run --help.
存在要传递的额外标志，并且可能只是 EXPOSE。
There is an extra flag that you have
to pass and it might just be EXPOSE.
EXPOSE，它是破折号 -P，我们走了。
EXPOSE, it's dash -P, there we go.
所以我要做的是我得说破折号 -P
So instead what I have to do, is I have
to say dash -P, which is gonna go and
把我放进去的所有港口都曝光了
expose all of those
ports that I put it on.
现在如果我说停手
And now if I say docker ps,
我真不知道哪个港口要曝光，就给我挑一个。
I actually don't know what port is going
to expose it, just picks one for me.
现在你可以看到我有 3000 ，它会进入容器中。
So you can see now that I have 3000,
which is gonna go into the container.
但从容器里出来的是 32768
But coming out of the container
is gonna be 32768.
所以现在我可以过来把它放在这里
So now, I can come over here and
put that in here And
它现在就会被映射到容器里
it works, right now,
it's mapping into the container.
这看起来不太方便吗
Does that seem less convenient?
我想大概是吧
I would assume it probably is, right?
而大多数人并不是出于这个原因而真正使用公开的。
And for the most part people don't
really use expose for this reason.
我听说有人说他们还会在这里曝光
I've heard some people say that they'll
still put expose in here just to let
大家都知道，就这样，就 3000，对吧 ?
people know is like hey, just so
you know, publish on 3000, right?
这才是我们期待的
That's what we're expecting here.
就像文档一样，你可以很容易地把它放在我的阅读中。
It's kinda like documentation, you can
easily just put that in the read me.
我不知道为什么你一定会把它放在 Docker 文件里。
I don't know why you'd necessarily
put it in the Docker file.
我不去 Docker 文件以获取文档。
I don't go to the Docker file for
documentation.
这就是 EXPOSE，当我开始使用 Docker时，这让我非常困惑，
So that's EXPOSE, that was very confusing
to me when I was starting out with Docker,
所以我想我希望能为你做点什么
so I thought I would hopefully
demystify that a little bit for you.
>> 所以发布什么 ?
&gt;&gt; So what does publish do?
它只是把它包在一起就像，嘿，你可以把它装船。
It just kind of packages it all together
and like, hey, you can ship this.
>> 因此发布如下 : 我内部有此端口，并且在外部具有此端口
&gt;&gt; So publish says like I have this port
internally and have this port externally
我希望你能把这两件事情都塞到一起
and I want you to plug those two things
together, like tunnel out together.
所以我可以把 8080 移植到端口 3000 的容器里
So I can port 8080 inside the container
published at the port 3000,
它会连接到这两个集装箱或者这两个港口，对吧 ?
it'll connect to those two containers or
those two ports, right?
所以它是端口映射，实际上它是一个端口映射。
So it's port mapping, it's literally
what it is, it's just port mapping.